(chuckles softly)
(Leonard:)Said the premise
is intriguing.
(Sheldon:)Good to see you again,
(Sheldon:)Mr. Stephen-Hawking-
Liked-Our-Paper.
(Leonard:)And you as well,
Mr. Our-Premise-
Is-Intriguing.
(Howard:)How do you do, Mr. I'll-
Admit-That's-Pretty-Cool?
(Raj:)Yeah, you keep
setting me up for failure.
"With a heavy heart,
"Amelia stood before
the newly repaired time machine.
(Penny:)She regretted giving Cooper
the part he needed."
Because she wanted
him to give her the
part she needed.
(Amy:)Okay, that's enough.
What?
No! I really want to know
what happens-- and Bernadette
(Penny:)really, really, really wants
to know what happens.
(Amy:)You're just making fun of me.
(Bernadette:)I was just kidding.
I'm sorry.
(Bernadette:)And the story's
really good!
No, it is!
Does he stay?
(Penny:)Do they kiss?
Does she find out about Montana?